<!DOCTYPE html>
<html lang="en">
<head>
    <meta charset="utf-8" />
    <meta name="description" content="Assignment 1" />
    <meta name="viewport" content="width=device-width, initial-scale=1"/>
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="https://cdnjs.cloudflare.com/ajax/libs/font-awesome/5.11.2/css/all.css"/>
    <link rel="stylesheet" href="style/style.css" />
    <title>Langkawi Island</title>
    
    <link rel="icon" href="./images/favcon.png" type="image/gif" sizes="16x16"/>
</head>
<body>
    <header>
        <div class="main">
            <div class="logo">
                <a href="./index.htm" target="_self" title="Homepage">
                    <img src="./images/PlanIt_logo2.png" alt="logo"/>
                </a>
            </div>
            <ul>
                <li class="active"><a href="Index.htm" target="_self" title="Homepage">Home</a></li>
                <li class="dropdown" id="menu"><a href="aboutus.html" class="dropbtn" target="_blank" title="About Plan It">About Us</a>
				  <div class="dropdown-content">
				 
						<select name="aboutus" id="aboutus">
						<option value="#">MEMBERS</option>
                                    <option href="profile1.html" value="profile1.html">ALEC</option>
                                    <option href="profile2.html" value="profile2.html">OLIVIA</option>
									<option href="profile3.html" value="profile3.html">NIGEL</option>
									<option href="profile4.html" value="profile4.html">JONATHAN</option>
						</select>
						
                                </div>
				</li>
				
                <li class="dropdown" id="menu"><a href="locations.html" class="dropbtn" target="_blank" title="Our vacation locations">Locations</a>
				<div class="dropdown-content">
				<select name="places" id="places">
                <option value="#">Places</option>
                                    <option href="product1.html" value="product1.html">Kuala Lumpur</option>
                                    <option href="product2.html" value="product2.html">Langkawi Islands</option>
									<option href="product3.html" value="product3.html">Sabah</option>
									<option href="product4.html" value="product4.html">Kuching</option>
						</select>
                                </div>
				</li>
                <li><a href="enquiry.html" target="_blank" title="Enquriy and Contacts">Enquiry</a></li>
                <li><a href="disclaimer.html" target="_blank" title="Disclaimer">Disclaimer</a></li>
                <li><a href="enhancements.html" target="_blank" title="Enhancement">Enhancement</a></li>

            </ul>
        </div>
    </header>

    <!--content starts here-->
    <div class="enhantextbox">
        <h1>LANGKAWI ISLAND</h1>
    </div>

    <div>
        <div class="heading2"></div>
        <div class="top">
            <img src="./images/langkawi.jpg" alt="PL" />
        </div>

        <div class="FP">
		<br/>
	       <fieldset class="field">
           <legend class="legend">Family Packages</legend>
            <img src='./images/skybridge.jpg' alt="Skybridge"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>The Langkawi Sky Bridge</strong><br/>The Langkawi Sky Bridge is located at the 'end' of the Cable Car ride. One of the island's highlights, it is a 410ft-long curved pedestrian bridge above Mount Mat Cinchang. It may sound like a cliche but it is really true - the views from here are simply stunning - great for those Kodak moments. Located 2,300ft above sea level, the Sky Bridge is easily accessible by the Langkawi Cable Car. The journey to the top starts out at the Oriental Village in the upper northwest of Langkawi Island, near Pantai Kok.
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
                <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            <hr />
            <br />
            <img src="Images/underwaterworld.jpg" alt="Underwater World"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>Underwater World Langkawi</strong><br/>The largest marine and fresh water aquaria in South East Asia, one must not miss the opportunity to experience walking through the tunnel displaying plenty of big fishes and sea creatures. First made its debut in August 1995, this attraction has attracted large number of locals as well as foreign tourists. The development of this underwater world has somehow further boost Langkawi's tourism.
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
                <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            </fieldset>
	   </div>

        <div class="CP">
		<br/>
	       <fieldset class="field">
           <legend class="legend">Couple Packages</legend>
            <img src='Images/ritz.jpg' alt="The Ritz-Carlton"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>The Ritz-Carlton Langkawi</strong><br/>Set within a 10-million-year-old rainforest on the edge of the Andaman Sea, The Ritz-Carlton, Langkawi ushers travelers into a pocket of the world where luxury and nature intersect. Hike through the dense, dynamic jungle or listen to the whispers of the forest from your sundeck. Kayak through mangroves, or simply gaze over the ocean during dinner. Whatever siren song calls to you in Malaysia, you will find its reply at this five-star resort.
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
                <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            <hr />
            <br />
            <img src="Images/datai.jpg" alt="The Datai"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>The Datai Langkawi</strong><br/>The Datai Langkawi is a captivating destination resort that blends into its natural surroundings. The resort's lush tropical rain forest embraces each room, suite, and villa, with private verandas offering breathtaking views. Datai bay is rated one of the top ten beaches in the world by National Geographic and together with the resort's surrounding jungle is host to a wealth of wildlife, some of which are endemic to the area.
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
                <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            </fieldset>
	   </div>

        <div class="HP">
		<br/>
	       <fieldset class="field">
           <legend class="legend">Honeymoon Packages</legend>
            <img src='Images/stregis.jpg' alt="The St. Regis Langkawi"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>The St. Regis Langkawi</strong><br/>Escape to a luxurious retreat nestled between centuries-old rainforest and the glistening calm Andaman Sea. The St. Regis Langkawi is a 5-star luxury resort in Langkawi, Malaysia, offering elegant suites and over-water villas with direct access to the beach and a spectacular sunset vista. Our bespoke guest experience includes the signature St. Regis Butler Service and its legendary rituals, transporting you to a world of pure resort luxury.
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
                <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            <hr />
            <br />
              <img src="Images/casa.jpg" alt="Casa Del Mar Langkawi"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>Casa Del Mar Langkawi</strong><br/>The 34-room Casa del Mar is an upscale Spanish-style property on Pantai Cenang beach -- near shops, restaurants, and bars -- offering its guests beachfront picnics and romantic candle-lit dinners. The restaurant and bar serve Mediterranean fare by the beach, outdoor pool, or hot tub. Spa pampering and water sports rentals are available on-site, and the gym offers a shower for guests checking out late. Pleasantly furnished suites include four-poster canopy beds, and some balconies offer sea views.
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
                <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            </fieldset>
	   </div>

        <div class="BP">
		<br/>
	       <fieldset class="field">
           <legend class="legend">Bestseller Packages</legend>
            <img src='Images/berjaya.jpg' alt="Berjaya Langkawi Resort"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>Berjaya Langkawi Resort</strong><br/>Set amidst a lush tropical rainforest, yet just steps away from the azure waters and a gorgeous beachfront, Berjaya Langkawi Resort is an invitation to a magical sojourn embraced by Mother Nature. Hailed as one of the best 5-star Langkawi resorts, our beachfront property offers a wide range of recreational activities such as sunset cruises, island tours, sea sports and more that will transcend you to a state of bliss.
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
                <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            <hr />
            <br />
            <img src="Images/templetree.jpg" alt="The Temple Tree"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>The Temple Tree</strong><br/>Temple Tree at Bon Ton is a charming four-pearl property located near the beach, with eight beautifully carved Malaysian villas built 70 to 110 years ago that can be rented as private homes or separate rooms. All of the rooms/villas feature private patios, mini-fridges, wooden bathtubs, flat-screen TVs, and free Wi-Fi, though it can be slow. The property -- with cats from the nearby shelter roaming around -- has two garden swimming pools, a restaurant and bar, billiard room, and a library with a computer.
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
                <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            </fieldset>
	   </div>

        <div class="FP">
		<br/>
	       <fieldset class="field">
           <legend class="legend">Festival Packages</legend>
            <img src='Images/waterfestival.jpg' alt="Langkawi International Water Festival"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>Langkawi International Water Festival</strong><br/>Held in April every year, the Langkawi International Water Festival is a water-sports competition designed as a tourism marketing event by the Langkawi Tourism Action Council and the Ministry Of Tourism Langkawi. Comprising an island-to-island kayak race, sandcastle-building competition, underwater treasure hunt, beach netball game, fishing competition and more, this event has been observed since 2002.
            <br />
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
            <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            <hr />
            <br />
            <img src="Images/tour.jpg" alt=" Tour De Langkawi"/>
            <div class="para"><strong>Tour De Langkawi</strong><br/>The Tour de Langkawi is a multiple stage bicycle race held in Malaysia. It is named after the archipelago Langkawi, where the first edition started and finished. The race has been held annually since 1996, primarily in February. It usually consists of 10-day-long segments (stages) over 10 days, but has been reduced to eight stages over recent years.
            <br />
            <br />
            <div class="enquire">
            <a href="enquiry.html">Enquire</a>
            </div>
            </div>
            </fieldset>
	   </div>
    </div>
	<br/>

    <footer>
        <div class="footer-container">
            <div class="left-col">
                <img src="images/PlanIt_logo2.png" alt="LOGO" class="logo"/>
                <div class="social-media">
                    <a href="https://www.facebook.com/traveloka.com.my/"><i class="fab fa-facebook-f"></i></a>
                    <a href="https://twitter.com/travelokaMY?ref_src=twsrc%5Egoogle%7Ctwcamp%5Eserp%7Ctwgr%5Eauthor"><i class="fab fa-twitter"></i></a>
                    <a href="https://www.instagram.com/travelokamy/?hl=en"><i class="fab fa-instagram"></i></a>
                    <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCk8XPjpvC_wXQhXrT5unl9Q"><i class="fab fa-youtube"></i></a>
                    <a href="https://id.linkedin.com/company/traveloka-com"><i class="fab fa-linkedin-in"></i></a>
                </div>
                <p class="rights-text"> PLAN IT &amp; TRAVEL | All Rights Reserved.</p>
            </div>


            <div class="footer-distributed">

                <div class="footer-left">
                    <h3>PLAN IT &amp; TRAVEL<span> Co.</span></h3>

                     <p class="footer-links">
                        <a href="Index.htm">Home</a>
                        |
                        <a href="aboutus.html">About Us</a>
                        |
                        <a href="location.html">Location</a>
                        |
                        <a href="enquiry.html">Contact Us</a>
                    </p>

                    <br/>
                    <br/>
                    <div class="right-col">
                        <h1>Our Newsletter</h1>
                        <div class="border"></div>
                        <p>Enter Your Email to get our news and updates.</p>
                        <form  class="newsletter-form">
                            <input type="text" class="txtb" placeholder="Enter Your Email"/>
                            <input type="submit" class="btn1" value="submit"/>
                        </form>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>
    </footer>
	<script src="./script/script.js"></script>
</body>


</html>
